Today, I’d like to recommend two things to you
to help discover and manage skills
Why release a video to recommend it?
Because it seems like no one reads the articles I wrote, uh
Both of these were released by Versal Lab
Let's take a look at this blog post
This blog post was published on January 20th.
It says here
We have released skills
This skills is a CLI tool
help us to install and manage skills
We'll take a closer look at this later
Let's finish reading the blog first
Here it says Excel I is used to install and manage skill packages
agent's package
Install the skill package
With this command, uh
So far
This skill has been installed and used
such as amp or those like cloud code
call bot
CodeX
Cursor
GM milk and the like
It has already been used by these.
Today we are also going to introduce a website
this is skills.sh
Let's click to check it out
Here it says it's a directory and a ranking list
skill leaderboard
Through it, we can discover some new skills
for our agent
Then browse the skills
by category and popularity
This passage is saying that through this thing to A install oh
Track usage statistics and installation status across the entire ecosystem
It says there's a simple command
and explore
He said let's add an official skill from Versal Lab
and explore this website
First, let's talk about VERSAL's official skill
He has developed a set of skills
However, this is more frontend-oriented.
and also leans towards react
It says here that the best practice for building is React
It contains some things, uh
also pretty good
which are some React specifications
and the use of cloud AI
and of course the web design guide
Also, regarding the VEE aspect, uh
Ansenfu released one of his SQ the other day
Of course, some parts of it are his own.
Here are the installation instructions
It shows that he has some formulas here like this skill, uh
He named it after himself
his preferences and best practices
such as INFLINT which is more PM-oriented
Of course, there are also some official skills
like VEE
some ecosystem libraries of skills in the VEE direction like next pinion
There are also some unofficial
Like, uh, SLIDAVE is something developed by Ansniv
and ts s down
Turbo Rapport
and view use
These view uses are also considered official
because the creator had just released it a few days ago
was officially included by Ansif as an official Skill
Next, let's talk about this website
First of all, this website is a platform for collecting and aggregating skills.
Then here you can see uh
All time
The top one is the find skill
We can take a look at this later
It also shows the most popular ones within 24 hours here
You can also see that this find skill is very popular
and this heart refers to the currently most popular skill
Then we can click into one to take a look
For example, take a look at this 'find' skill
It helps us discover skills through this skill
What does it mean
is through our human natural language
For example, what should I do
what kind of skill is needed
help me find a skill or similar terms uh
to help us find a suitable skill
and install and use
Of course, let's take a look at its detailed interface.
Here are the basic installation commands
Then skill.md introduces what it is used for
some commands
and so on
but here is its weekly usage
download
Of course, here is its usage distribution
for example in cloud code
how much is used in Open Code
and also the first time uh
it can be said to be released
or say it was first seen nine days ago
And here is its repository
corresponds to the Skill CLI we just mentioned
Because it is not just a management tool
and it can help us discover that it has some commands
such as basic addition
and to find out which skills we currently have installed
This find is our find_skill to search for some skills
through some keywords
delete skill
then check its update status
update skill
This checks whether it can be updated.
This is to directly update
Here we are creating a new sq md template
This should be when we create the skill ourselves
This can be used to quickly generate a template
Um
Now let's give it a try
For example, let's install Antoniev's set of skills
then paste it in to install
It is now installing these skills
And here we can choose to install all
Then it prompts me to select a platform
I'll just use Open Code.
find open code, um
nothing else
Choose direct installation
Here it has a soft link
And this is also easy to update
So we'll choose the first one
Confirm installation
The installation is now complete here
Then we can use this to test it out
For example, we can use NPX
Skills list
to check what we have installed
OK, it lists what was just installed here.
Of course, we usually check the global
all require Gangji to view the global installation
For example, I'll take these oh
Let me not delete it yet
Let me first check with skuse check
Here it is checking their update status
Everything is up to date
for example, I'll execute it
Here it starts checking
then if it can be updated
it will update to the latest version
For example, I'll delete them all
Remove
I'll just delete them all
Here it shows the deletion is complete
Then let's check again
it's gone
He said look here it says
To view global skills
add a -g flag
Now let's find a skill
npx skills find
for example V13
Oh, here he gave us this list
and then gives us a command
Then we can add it here, uh
for example
Let me install this one.
OK it starts installing
Ah, it's asking me to select a platform here
then it defaults to selecting open code
I'll just randomly select one
Then just wait for the installation to complete.
Then we'll delete it
Then let's try to create one
For example, I go under my project
then ng x gift meat
Let's play VEE again
OK then it created our LS let's take a look
Here we have a directory we can cd into
Open it with vs code and take a look
Here it has initialized a skill template for me
That's all for this video.